{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What's the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      "options": ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "React was created by...",
      "options": ["Andrew Clark", "Dan Abramov", "Jason Bonta", "Jordan Walke"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the building blocks of React?",
      "options": ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the XML-like JavaScript extension syntax used in React?",
      "options": ["YAML", "JSON", "JSX", "Babel"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the one-way data flow work in React?",
      "options": [
        "Parent to child",
        "Child to parent",
        "A and B",
        "The developer decide"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How do React components communicate with each other?",
      "options": ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When we can use the derived state in React",
      "options": [
        "The state doesn't have to trigger re-render",
        "The state has to memoize some computations based only on the current props",
        "The state has to be accessible to all the components",
        "The state has to be computed based on the existing state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When does a component trigger re-rendering in React?",
      "options": [
        "Running an Effect",
        "Passing props",
        "Updating a state",
        "Calling a function"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When we can directly manipulate the DOM in React?",
      "options": [
        "Optional",
        "Changing the UI",
        "Adding styles",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When do we have to pass a function to setState in React?",
      "options": [
        "Updating the state will be slow",
        "The updated state is very data-intensive",
        "Updating the state has to happen faster",
        "The new state is computed based on the previous state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "If we pass a function as \"initialState\", when will React call our initializer function?",
      "options": [
        "Re-renders",
        "Each time the state is updated",
        "Initializing the component",
        "The first time the state is updated"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "We want to control a non-React component based on the React state.",
      "options": ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which values have to be declared as a dependency in an Effect?",
      "options": [
        "Usually none",
        "All the states",
        "Every reactive value used by the Effect's code",
        "All the values required for cleanup"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "An Effect will always run on the initial render.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "It depends on the dependency",
        "False",
        "In depends on the code in the Effect"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "If an Effect doesn't have a dependency, When will the Effect run?",
      "options": [
        "The component mounts",
        "The component unmounts",
        "The first time the component re-rendered",
        "Each time the component is re-rendered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
